CURRICULUM VITAE

Ujval Pradipkumar Shah

Address : A-503, Satsang Residency, Opp. Aypjannagar True Value Showroom, Hathijan -382445.

Email ID : Ujval.shah25@gmail.com

Mobile No. : + 91 8866478803

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am seeking for the position of Team Management to enhance my knowledge, experience and skills. To gain experience for Team handling position and utilize my Core skills, as I have enough experience of ground level management and individuality so that I can guide team to increase their productivity and help organization to increase revenue.

PROFESSIONAL SYNOPSIS

A dynamic professional with **11 years** of experience in Sales and distribution. A skillful person with good market knowledge, command over different languages and willing to work with great opportunities as well as accepting the challenges with working under different conditions and environment and a perfect candidate for the post of your needful place to fulfill your criteria and expectations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bharti Airtel Limited - Account Manager

(Feb 2023 - Present)

Job Responsibility: -

- My responsibility is to ensure sales and service in my assigned territory to deliver Data (Internet Bandwidth, MPLS, Cloud etc.), Voice (Postpaid), Broadband and Fixed Line Business. Front-end the relationship with customer from Airtel side and become the single point of contact for customer for all three lines of business.
- New account break-in (hunting) for Data, Voice and Fixed Line.
- Cross-sell multi-product lines in existing and new customer Build & maintain healthy funnel for all three Lines of Business with earmarked levels of maturity.

GTPL Hathway Limited - Senior BDE (Sales Executive & Operation)

(August 2020 to March 2022)

Job Responsibility: -

- Developing growth strategies and managing and retaining relationships with existing clients.
- Drafting, Writing and reviewing business proposals and negotiating with stakeholders.
- Identifying and mapping business strengths and customer needs locally and internationally.
- Adds notes to records for each client call or meeting.
- Tracks every media purchase made to ensure that it is completed accurately and on time.
- Works to maximize sales and meet quotas in the short and long term.
- Maintains excellent relationships with all clients in the executive's portfolio.

Hinduja Globle Solution Pvt. Ltd. (ICICI Merchant Service) - Business counselor

(Nov 2019 To Aug 2020)

Job Responsibility: -

- Plan, organize and manage business projects for clients
- Based on clients' requirements, work on projects related to recruiting, payroll, production, budgeting, promotional campaigns, etc.
- Perform initial assessments for each client before the project begins and collect as much information about the client's business as possible and try to understand clients' needs and wants and then pitch product according to the client requirement.
- Perform research using shadowing, interviews, surveys, reading reports, etc.
- Develop detailed business plans.

I Venus (Apple Store) - Sales Export (Sales Marketing)

(April 2017 To July 2019)

Job Responsibility: -

- Represent our company, with a comprehensive understanding of our offerings, Maximize the sales performance by establishing strong relationships and gaining insight to the needs and lifestyle of the client and Meet weekly, monthly, and annual sales and activity quotas.
- Generate leads and commit to customer service by building relationships.
- Adjust sales techniques based on interactions and results in the field.
- Perform incisive and insightful market and competitive research.
- Qualify, develop, and maintain thorough company and product knowledge, research consumer needs, and identify how our solutions can meet them.
- Generate leads and grow existing relationships, maintaining an accurate, detailed client book, and developing an active, repeat customer base.
- Make cold calls or perform warm outreach, putting outside-the-box thinking to work to develop new and unique sales tactics.
- Work with the Account Executive team to design industry-specific outbound efforts.

Kataria Automobiles Pvt. Ltd. - Sales Representative

(March 2015 To March 2017)

Job Responsibility: -

- Utilize Salesforce.com tool to ensure standard processes during all sales stages
- Greet and assist customers as they shop for new products.
- Suggest applicable and relevant up sells to help customers walk out the door with everything they need
- Meet weekly, monthly and quarterly sales quotas
- Prepare and submit weekly sales reports to management
- Assist other team members with transactions when necessary.

Reliance Digital - Sales Representative

(March 2013 To Feb 2015)

Job Responsibility: -

- Builds business by identifying and selling prospects maintaining relationships with clients.
- Identifies business opportunities by identifying prospects and evaluating their position in the industry researching and analyzing sales options.
- Sells products by establishing contact and developing relationships with prospects recommending solutions.
- Maintains relationships with clients by providing support, information, and guidance researching and recommending new opportunities recommending profit and service improvements.
- Identifies product improvements or new products by remaining current on industry trends, market activities, and competitors.
- Prepares reports by collecting, analyzing, and summarizing information.
- Maintains quality service by establishing and enforcing organization standards.
- Maintains professional and technical knowledge by attending educational workshops; reviewing professional
 publications establishing personal networks benchmarking state of the art practices participating in professional
 societies.

Education

- ✓ **B.COM** from Gujarat University in 2014.
- ✓ **H.S.C** from Gujarat Board in 2011.
- ✓ **S.S.C** from Gujarat Board in 2009.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date Of Birth : 29th Aug 1994

Marital Status : Unmarried

Hobbies: To meet new persons, to learn new things, Traveling

Language Proficiency: Gujarati, Hindi, English.